cobone.com 2014-02-13

# Cobone: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

COBONE.com FZ-LLC ("COBONE") is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. The COBONE team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling or where we have your express permission to do so.

**Triperna**  
We are in the process of re-branding our existing Cobone Destinations offers and relocating them. All your favourite travel specials and more will soon be available at Triperna.com Please note: we will be communicating with you via email regarding the launch of Triperna.com. You may opt out of these communications at any point, as per this privacy policy.

**Your Consent**  
When you register to Cobone.com you will be providing a limited amount of information which we will store in a secure environment. The data that we hold for each customer is used in order to serve better content to each customer. Below is a list detailing what kind of information we store:

  * Name and contact details
  * Transaction history
  * Communications record 
  * Profile: age, gender, profession, income, hobbies
  * Spending habits

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission, but we cannot be responsible or held liable for the actions of third party sites from which you may have linked or been directed to the COBONE website.

**Communication & Marketing**  
If you have registered on COBONE we will update you on our daily deals, news and special offers via e-mail, post or telephone.

We may share your information with COBONE Merchants. From time to time, we provide offers from particular merchants (referred to as “COBONE Merchants”) who, as part of the offer, request information on COBONE customers who purchased the offer in order to aid redemption. In those cases, we share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with COBONE Merchants. Sharing this Information may allow a COBONE Merchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with a COBONE Merchant if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the COBONE Merchant involved in that Identification Activity. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such COBONE Merchant. While we inform them that they are only permitted to communicate with you for the purposes of the specific promotion with COBONE, we do not have any responsibility for the actions of the COBONE Merchant, and the actions of the COBONE Merchant are not in our control. 

**Opt out**  
All COBONE members have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us and/or selected third parties you should click on the link located at the bottom of the email and follow the instructions in order to be removed from all future mailing. Alternatively you can opt-out by visiting 'My Data' in 'Your Account' on the COBONE website. You can access 'Your Account' once you are logged in to your COBONE account.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website and it will recognise your device on future visits. These types of files do a number of different jobs such as remembering your preferences and chosen items, assisting you to improve your site experience as well as trying to ensure that the adverts or offers you see online are more relevant to you. These “cookies” can be divided into 4 types each of which is outlined below.

**Category 1: Strictly Necessary Cookies**  
These cookies are essential in order to enable the site to provide services you have asked for such as remembering your shopping bag items.

**Category 2: Performance Cookies**  
This type collect anonymous information on how people use the site and the data is merged with other users to enable us to improve how the site operates. For example we utilise Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our site, browse or use our site and highlight areas where we can improve areas such as navigation, shopping experience and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.

**Category 3: Functionality Cookies**  
These remember choices you make such as language, deal interests or currency. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate with your selections and make the visits more tailored and pleasant. The information is also merged with other users on an anonymous basis to enable us to improve how the site operates.

**Category 4: Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies**  
These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers. For example we use 3rd party companies such as iKoo to provide you with more personalised adverts when visiting other websites.

You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer or mobile device without your explicit consent. Your browser “help” section will normally provide details on how to manage the cookie settings.

**Protecting your security**  
We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity.

**Transfers of your Information**  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal data, but cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Disclosures of your information**  
We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * in the event that COBONE sells or buys any business or assets;
  * if COBONE or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets; or
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of COBONE, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Third party sites**  
Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Checking your Details**  
If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to COBONE you may do so by contacting us via the e-mail address or address given below. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.

**Contacting us**  
We are always pleased to hear from our customers (even if it is a complaint!). We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied - we want you to return to the site and to recommend us to your friends and family. If you have any questions or feedback about this statement, or if you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact a customer service member of the COBONE team, who will be delighted to answer any questions you may have.

You can either contact our customer care team at support.cobone@cobone.com   
or, write to us at:

Cobone.com  
Dubai Internet City  
EIB Building 03  
2nd floor Office 203  
PO Box 502983  
Dubai, UAE

Or By Phone:  
UAE: +97144554600  
Saudi Arabia: +920005949
